wyfegypt.com 2019-05-11

# World Youth Forum

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you register on this website.

* * *

## User Rights under the General Data Protection Regulation

The General Data Protection Act (GDPR) is a set of privacy and digital security regulations enacted by the European Commission which sets out to provide some basic protections to personal and sensitive data of EU residents. 

By registering on the website to attend the forum, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.register.wyfegypt.com 

* * *

## Information Collection And Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to complete your registration process.

### Types of Data Collected

#### Personal Data

While registering on our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * Email address 
  * First name, last name and name as in passport 
  * Phone number
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
  * Country of residence 
  * Passport details and scan copy 
  * Profile photo 
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City 
  * Education and Job Details 
  * Emergency Contact Details 
  * Cookies and Usage Data

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information how the website is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our website and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of the website.

Examples of Cookies we use:

  * **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our website.
  * **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

* * *

## Use of Data

WYF Egypt uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To complete your registration process. 
  * To notify you about your registration status 
  * To issue your WYF ID 
  * To book your accommodation and flight tickets 
  * To provide customer care and support. 
  * To monitor the website access
  * To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service. 
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To notify you regarding future events 

* * *

## Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Egypt and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Egypt and process it there. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

WYF Egypt will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

* * *

## Disclosure Of Data

### Legal Requirements

WYF Egypt may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of WYF Egypt
  * To protect against legal liability

* * *

## Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

* * *

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate your journey to WYF performing related services. 

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

* * *

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

* * *

## Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

* * *

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

* * *

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: Inquiry@wyfegypt.com
  * By visiting this page on our website: https://www.wyfegypt.com/Privacy Policy
